brickunderground.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy

**Brick Underground Privacy Policy**

Last modified: October 23, 2018

This Brick Underground Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** ”) outlines the information that Brick Underground LLC (the **“Company”** , “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”) gathers when you visit the website [https://www.brickunderground.com](https://www.brickunderground.com/) (our “ **Website** ”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

_**Information We Collect About You**_

We collect information about you when you provided it to us directly or through automatic information technologies.

_Information You Provide to Us Directly_ **.**

We collect several types of information directly from you, including:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of posting comments, or subscribing to marketing materials as well as records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

_Automatic Information Collection Technologies_ **.**

We use automatic data collection technologies to collect and store information about your equipment, browsing actions, details of your visits to our Website and information about your computer and internet connection such as your IP address, operating system, and browser type. Collection of this type of information helps us to improve this Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to, among other things:

  * estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
  * store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize this Website according to your individual interests;
  * speed up your searches; and
  * recognize you when you return to the Website.

The technologies we and our service providers use for automatic data collection may include:

  * **Browser Cookies.** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

_**Information Collected by Third Parties.**_

We use a number of service providers to help us operate the Website and our newsletter. For instance our Website contains affiliate marketing links which means that we get paid commission on sales of those products or services (although these marketing partners do not control what we write in our own editorial content), we rely on a third party to manage the comments section of our Website, and we allow third party ad networks to use automatic data collection technologies to collect information about you for purposes of providing interest-based ads. Some of these providers may access information about you via automatic data collection technologies and may use cookies, web beacons, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from our Website, our e-mails, and elsewhere on the internet.

Some (but not all) of our third-party partners are identified below:

  * **Google.** We use Google’s products for the purpose of collecting information about traffic to our Website and how users use our Website. To learn more about how these products collect and process data and the choices Google may offer to control these activities, visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).
  * **Quantcast.** **** We use Quantcast products for the purpose of purpose of collecting information about traffic to our Website and how users use our Website. To learn more about how Quantcast products collect and process data and choice Quantcast may offer to control these activities, visit <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy>.
  * **SkimLinks.** We work with SkimLinks as an affiliate marketing partner. To learn more about the information Skimlinks collects and how it uses this information please review their privacy policy at <http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy>. To opt out of Skimlinks, visit [https://optout.skimlinks.com](https://optout.skimlinks.com/).
  * **Clicky.** We use Clicky to log and analyze the traffic to our web site. You may review Clicky's privacy policy at <http://clicky.com/terms/privacy>.
  * **Disqus.** The comments section of our website is controlled and powered by Disqus, Inc. If you would like more information about how they use and collect your information and how to access and correct your information please review their privacy policy at <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>.

_Please Note_ : We do not control third party tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about any of our third-party partners, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

_**Links to Third Party Websites and Social Media Widgets**_

This Website and some of our electronic communications to you may contain links to other websites that are owned and operated by third parties. Links to third parties from this Website are not an endorsement by us. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy and security practices of these third parties. We recommend that you review the privacy and security policies of these third parties to determine how they handle information they may collect from or about you.

This Website may also include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and the page you are visiting on this Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure the feature functions properly. Your interactions with these features and the information from or about you collected by them are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

_**How We Use Your Information**_

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information you request from us, such as our newsletter.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To communicate with you about our own and third parties’ products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * To display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences.
  * To understand the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming and other activities;
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

_**Disclosure of Your Information**_

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures.
  * To third-party advertising companies, which may collect information about you and your online activities on our Website over time and across third-party websites and applications. These companies use the information they collect to help advertisers identify and serve ads to you that are more relevant to you.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://www.brickunderground.com/terms-of-use).
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, those who visit our Website, or others.

_**Individuals Under the Age of 18**_

We do not knowingly collect data from children under 18 nor do we permit under our Terms of Use any person to use our Website who is not at least 18 years old. If we learn that we have received identifying information from a user under the age of eighteen, we will delete this information.

_**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**_

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s [website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

  * Opt Out of Online Behavioral Advertising. We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. For information about opt out programs that third-party advertising companies participate in, and to opt out of the use of website browsing data for interest-based advertising by companies that participate in these programs, you can visit [ www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) to learn more.  You can also visit the DAA Consumer Choice Page at [http://youradchoices.com](http://youradchoices.com/) and download AppChoices free of charge to enable desktop data collection control. Please note that when using the ad industry opt-out tools described above, we may still collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes and you may continue to receive ads but those ads will be less relevant because they won’t be tailored to your interests.  In addition, if you use multiple browsers or devices you may need to execute this opt out on each browser or device.

  * **Promotional Offers from the Company and Third Parties.** If you do not wish to have your email address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#51253934332338323a2534303c11332338323a243f35342336233e243f357f323e3c). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may also send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.

  * **Accessing and Correcting Your Information.** If there are any changes or updates to your account information, or if you would like to delete your personal information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f7839f9295859e949c8392969ab795859e949c8299939285908598829993d994989a). _Please note_ : certain federal and state regulations require that we maintain a record of your information for certain periods of time. Due to these regulations, we may be unable to completely delete your information from our database until the time requirements of these regulations have expired.

_**Visiting this Website from Outside the United States**_

This Website is designed for individuals in the United States. If you are visiting this Website from outside the United States or are not a US resident, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The information protection laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive or protective as those in your country. By using this Website and our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy.

_**Your California Privacy Rights**_

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c2b6aaa7a0b0aba1a9b6a7a3af82a0b0aba1a9b7aca6a7b0a5b0adb7aca6eca1adaf) or write us at: Brick Underground, LLC; 349 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY 10016.

_**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**_

Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. We currently do not recognize browser Do Not Track Signals. Please use the following link to learn more about DNT: [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

_**Data Security**_

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

_**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**_ ****

If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through our Website. We encourage you to periodically visit our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

_**Contact Information**_ ****

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Brick Underground, LLC  
349 Fifth Avenue  
New York NY 10016  
646-701-7038

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#17637f7275657e747c6372767a5775657e747c62797372657065786279733974787a)
